原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
翻|校|监     外甥女草    时间轴   无关风粤     后期     拉图
哈兰·科本原著改编
陌生人
第一季 第六集
警察
钥匙链属于柯琳·普莱斯  19年5月16日上报失踪
奥莉薇娅
我妈妈明天晚上18:30到21:30不在
甜心
凯蒂发给马贝克40的新信息
我一直在想你  你一直想做的那件事...
拨号  凯兹
道德分享
甜心
马贝克40
...考虑了
你是我唯一会愿意
与之做那事的人
我愿做
我想把自己交给你
我们实现你最深的欲望吧
凯蒂  亲
凯蒂  你不会后悔的
去波利塔酒吧见我
下午5:45  马贝克40
道德分享  两通未接来电
道德分享
你有两条新留言
马上打给我
紧急  你被设局了
道德分享
接电话
别到波利塔来
老鼠药
接待处
我需要你帮忙
I need your help.
马丁·吉连要求见你  事实上
Martin Killane has asked to see you. In fact...
他只肯跟你说话
he will only talk to you.
我很久以前做了件很坏的事
I did a terrible thing a long time ago.
开始做必须要做的事之前
And before what has to happen begins...
我想跟你说说这件事
I wanted to tell you about it.
因为我只信任你
Because you're the only person I trust.
你能理解吗
Does that make sense?
谢谢
Thank you.
你见过我妻子的照片  娜塔莎
You've seen photos of my wife, Natasha.
她出现时  我以为我是这世上最幸运的男人
I thought I was the luckiest man alive when she came along.
她是那么美丽
She was so gorgeous and...
难以驾驭  不好迎合
challenging and demanding.
她颠覆了我的世界
She turned my world upside down.
我崇拜她  我非常崇拜她
I adored her, I completely adored her.
但她渴求...
But, uh, she needs...
关注
attention, and...
而我是个整天忙碌的警察
I'm a cop working all hours.
所以她去找其他男人
So she meets other men.
我无法接受
And I can't handle it.
我说  "够了  我受够了"
And I say, "That's it, that's it." And...
她说  "不
she says, "No.
他们不算什么  你才是我的唯一
They're nothing. You're one, the only one.
只有你和我
It's you and me.
我们生个孩子吧"
Let's have a baby."
我们就生了
And we do.
克里斯出生时
And when Chris comes along...
这孩子改变了一切
this baby changes everything.
我都迷住了
I'm besotted.
我总处于一种难以置信的状态
I'm in a constant state of amazement.
养大这孩子
Raising this child...
成了我人生的意义
that's the meaning of life.
但是
But...
娜塔莎做不来
Natasha can't handle it.
她觉得太难了
She finds it hard.
所以我很重要
So I'm important.
能有这么个
And... to have this...
可爱的小孩跑向我
adorable toddler running towards me,
每次我回家都拥抱我
arms out every time I come home...
然后有次  有天  我早回家了
Then one time, one day, I come home early and...
娜塔莎打了一堆行李
Natasha has all these bags packed.
她站在那里
She's standing there.
我逮住了她
I've caught her, right?
她说
And she tells me...
她要离开我了  她要走了
that she's leaving me, she's going,
她还要带走克里斯
and she's taking Chris with her.
她对我说的那些话啊
Oh, the things she said to me.
我不知该说什么  我无语了
And I'm lost for words, I'm speechless.
然后她抓起克里斯
And then she grabs Chris...
开始往外走  她正要走  我爆发了
and starts to go, is actually going, and I lash out.
娜塔莎倒下了
And Natasha goes down.
她倒下了
She goes down, and...
我抱起了克里斯
I pick up Chris and...
去了别的房间  关上了门
go into the other room and close the door.
我...
And I...
我真的还想着  再回去跟她理论
I really thought I was going back to reason with her.
但她一开口  说要带走克里斯
But as soon as she spits out at me that she's taking Chris...
我一拳拳地
I land a second, a third,
不停地...
fourth, a fifth blow and...
然后
And...
就结束了
And it's over.
结束了
It was over.
你会那么做吗
Would you do the like of that...
为了救你爱的人
to save the one you loved?
比如柯琳
Like Corinne, say?
因为可怕的是
Because the terrible thing is...
我从没想到自己能做出这样的事
I never thought I'd be capable of such a thing.
但我现在知道了
I... But I know now
为了保住那孩子  我还会那么做的
that I would do the same again to keep that child.
之后的事就不难了
And what followed wasn't hard.
我办过那么多凶杀案
I've been on so many murder cases, I...
我清楚怎么藏尸体
I know how to hide a body.
包起来
Wrap it up,
封得密不透风  敲开一面墙
seal it so it's airtight, open up a wall,
把尸体放进去
put the body in the wall,
再把墙砌好  恢复如初
patch it up so it's good as new.
难道没人
Did nobody...
找她吗
miss her?
嗯  她买了火车票
Yeah, well, she bought train tickets.
她...
She...
取了钱
had withdrawn cash.
她还跟人说了她要走
She'd even told people that she was going.
丢下孩子
Leaving the child behind, that...
那让大家很震惊
that really shocked people.
什么样的妈妈会那么做  但是
What kind of mother does the like of that? But...
我让人们同情了我  所以我没被怀疑过
I pulled people over to my side, so I was never suspected.
我离开了警队  开始做全职老爸
I gave up the force and threw myself into being a full-time dad,
我很喜欢
which I loved.
你也知道小孩子什么样
You know what young kids are like.
总是要这要那
They can never have enough.
我奉献了一切
And I gave everything.
I gave everything.
我想那么做
I wanted to.
讽刺的是
And the irony is...
我自己养大的孩子已经很多年没跟我说过话了
that child I raised all on my own hasn't spoken to me for years.
那柯琳呢
What about Corinne?
什么
What?
她在哪
Where is she?
尸体被发现时  你...
When the body was found, you...
看着我  你说"对不起"
looked at me and you said, "I'm sorry."
因为我利用了你
For using you.
是的
Yes.
要不我为什么会那么说
Why else would I say that?
是因为我
This is about me
和我对娜塔莎做的事
and what I did to Natasha.
是我和娜塔莎
It's about me and Natasha
还有...
and... and...
还有克里斯
and Chris.
我以为你会理解
I thought you'd understand that.
我告诉你我理解什么
I'll tell you what I understand.
你养大了你孩子的房子
You raised your child in a house
也是你在墙里埋孩子妈妈尸体的地方
with the corpse of their mother buried in the walls.
这就是我理解的事
That's what I understand.
-亚当  -不
- Adam... - No.
亚当
Adam!
能分享一下吗
Able to share anything?
我需要跟格里芬警长谈谈
I need to speak to DS Griffin.
好  把吉连带回牢房
Right. Get Killane back to his cell.
嗯  格里芬警长在找凯兹
Yeah. DS Griffin wants to know where Katz is.
非常感谢
Thank you so much. Thank you so much.
认识你很高兴
Good to meet you.
-认识你很高兴  -太好了
- Good to meet you. - Lovely.
-做得好  -谢谢
- Well done. - Thank you.
那两个主教是教会专员
Those two bishops are church commissioners.
而且
And...
我觉得他们会在发布前资助应用
I think they're gonna endorse the app in time for the launch.
-那太好了  -天大的好事
- Well, that's wonderful. - Oh, huge.
道德投资  人人可为
Ethical investing within everyone's reach.
想想看  将本地教堂作为募集点
Imagine, local churches as collection points
让最穷的教区居民能分享财富创造
so the poorest parishioner can share in wealth creation.
就像关于寡妇力量的寓言
It's the parable of the widow's might,
但寡妇既接受也付出
but where the widow receives as well as gives.
简直再好不过
Couldn't be better.
凯兹先生
Mr. Katz?
-你好  -鲍尔斯太太
- Hello. - Oh, Mrs. Powers.
你需要喝杯茶吗
Can I get you a tea or anything?
不了  亲爱的
Uh, no, sweetheart.
不  帕特里克不多待
No, Patrick isn't staying.
他就走  但谢谢你了
It's just a flying visit. But thank you.
-我就回去  -好
- I'll be right in. - Oh, right.
那下次见  凯兹先生
See you next time, Mr. Katz.
见到你很高兴  鲍尔斯太太  保重
It's good to see you, Mrs. Powers. Take care.
那么
And...
我的保安主管还带来好消息了吗
is my head of security also the bearer of good news?
一切
Is...
都解决了吗
everything resolved?
我还在解决
I'm working on it.
什么意思
What do you mean?
帕特里克  道德分享不仅是我的公司
Patrick, Ethical Share isn't only a company,
还是我的生活
it's my life.
我们要发布我的生活了
We're launching my life--
鲍尔斯先生  你们公司要支付
Mr. Powers, your company's gonna be paying
我女儿的医疗费
for my daughter's medical care,
所以我清楚事关多么重大
so I know how much this matters.
那拜托告诉我你已经完成任务
Then please tell me you've done your job
教训过这些勒索者了
and shut these blackmailers down.
我给我们争取了时间
I've bought us some time.
什么  怎么说
What? How?
我从一个失踪老师的教室拿了个钥匙链
I got a key fob from a missing teacher's classroom
留给我同事去发现  他们也发现了
and planted it for my colleagues to find, which they did.
那大大分散了他们的注意力  但
It's been the perfect diversion. But...
你没把一切告诉我  是吧
you didn't tell me the whole story, did you?
这里面是那个妈妈遭勒索的女孩
This details every communication and liaison we had
全部的通讯和联系详情
with that girl whose mother was blackmailed.
谢谢  谢了
Thank you. Ta.
你可不是只见了她一次两次
You didn't just see her once or twice.
她见了她34次
You saw her 34 times.
他们能通过这个查到我吗
Can they identify me through this?
除非我先找到他们  我会的
Not if I get to them first, which I will.
但为此  我需要两千
But for that, I need two grand.
干什么  不能留踪迹  我们绝不能有丑闻
For what? Nothing traceable. We can't have any scandal.
是为了支付一个银行朋友
No, it's to pay a banking contact
能为我们追踪海蒂·道伊尔的勒索钱
who can track the Heidi Doyle blackmail money for us.
然后  等我知道该找谁
Then, as soon as I know who to call on,
问题就解决了
the problem is over.
什么意思  你要干什么
Why? What will you do?
我是个警察
I'm a policeman.
他们是勒索犯
They're blackmailers.
他们会消失掉的
They'll simply melt away.
吉连怎么说
What did Killane say?
是他妻子  娜塔莎
It's his wife, Natasha.
很早以前杀了她
Killed way back.
吉连干的吗
By Killane?
她要离开他
She was gonna leave him.
我看到墙里的尸体时  还以为是柯琳
When I saw the body in the wall, I thought it was Corinne.
你妻子的车在机场附近被发现了
Your wife's car has been found up by the airport.
我们在监视  看是否有人再去  但...
We're watching it, seeing if anyone returns to it, but...
-跟我来  我们去看看  -你确定吗
- Come with me. Let's take a look. - You sure about this?
是的
Yeah.
你接管这里
You take over here.
跟我来
Come with me.
那再回奥莉薇娅家吗
So back to Olivia's then, yeah?
最好是
I think we should.
她明明在家  她妈却说她在医院
I mean, her mom's saying she's in hospital when she's not.
-还扔了那么多药  -和老鼠药
- Chucking out all those medicines. - And rat poison.
别忘了老鼠药
Don't forget the rat poison.
我们可以巧妙地提一句
We can just slip it in casually, you know?
吃了很多药吧
Medicines, yeah.
你家现在闹鼠患吗
And do you have a rodent problem at the moment?
我只想让你听到奥莉薇娅承认
Look, I just want you to hear Olivia admit
是她告诉我
that she's the one who told me
是你发了埃拉的照片
you posted the Ella photos,
你就知道我为什么要给你的大麻卷下药了  好吗
so then you know why I spiked your joint, okay?
妈妈  一小时后回来  好吗
Mom, back in an hour or so, okay?
好
Okay.
托马斯  你爸叫我给瑞恩做饭
Oh, Thomas, your dad's asked me to feed Ryan,
你也回来吃晚饭吗
so if you wanna come back for dinner?
嗯  好  谢谢
Yeah, okay, thanks.
提醒我永远别坐你的车
Remind me to never get in your car.
你没事吧
You all right?
在柯琳
You know, before Corinne...
假怀孕之前
faked her pregnancy...
我接了桩案子
I had taken on a case
跟另一位女律师一起
with another lawyer, a woman.
然后
And...
我们经常在一起
we spent a lot of time together...
你懂的
you know...
我们走得很近
got pretty close.
我当时没想到  但是...
It didn't occur to me at the time, but...
或许柯琳
maybe Corinne...
以为我的心不在家里了
thought that my attention was elsewhere
所以她才那么做了
and that's why she did what she did.
或许  或许不是
Maybe, maybe not.
谁知道呢
Who knows?
听着  我们都
Look, we all...
会搞砸关系
mess up relationships.
我们并不想伤害我们爱的人
We're not trying to hurt the ones we love.
但我们还是会伤害他们
But we do.
就在那里  停在了那里
It's up there, that's where it's parked.
嗯  那是...
Yeah, that's...
她的车
that's her car.
你妻子带护照了吗
Did your wife take her passport with her?
应该没有吧
I wouldn't have thought so, no.
你或她  去机场时会停在这里吗
And did you or she ever park here when using the airport?
从不
Never.
或许她没电了
Maybe she ran out of charge.
我们得先看看后备箱
We need to look in the boot first.
我有钥匙  等等
I've got a key. Hang on.
好
Okay.
抱歉  你得待在这里
I'm sorry, you need to stay there.
真是我见过的最干净的后备箱了
It's the neatest boot I've ever seen.
-太棒了  -是你的了
- Oh, it's just lovely. - All yours.
-她喜欢的  -好干净啊
- She loves it. - It's so clean.
有什么不寻常的吗
Anything unusual?
后座上那个是什么
What's that there on the back seat?
那是柯琳的耳环
Yeah, that's Corinne's earring.
我给她买的
Ones that I bought her.
怎么在这里
What's it doing there?
怎么会在这里
Why would it be there?
首先  她会戴着这个吗
First things first, would she be wearing them?
是的  她从不摘的  很喜欢
Yes, she never takes them off. She loves them.
-亚当  对不起  -拜托  找到她吧
- Adam, look, I'm sorry. I know-- - Please, just find her for me.
好了  奥莉薇娅
Right, Olivia...
我需要你告诉迈克你在狂欢上对我说的话
I need you to tell Mike what you told me at the rave.
因为他不相信我
'Cause he doesn't believe me.
那对我们是个问题
That's a problem for us.
好了  我觉得这样是不行的
Okay. I don't think this is the way to go about this.
只能如此
It's the only way.
奥莉薇娅
Olivia...
你当时在找我  是吧
you were looking for me, right?
你来找到了我  是吧
You came and found me, yes?
黛茜
Daisy?
什么事
What?
-网上那些埃拉的照片  -那不是埃拉的
- Those Ella photos posted online-- - Yeah, they're not of Ella.
我知道  是迈克干的
No, I know. But it was Mike.
在学校的储物柜旁  大家都在拿东西
At school, by the lockers, everyone's getting their stuff.
他在一旁  拿手机看些恶心的特写色情照片
And he's to the side, looking at these gross close-up porn shots.
然后他把手机放进了埃拉包里  就走了
But then he slips it in Ella's bag, walks off.
接着又从自己的兜里拿了手机出来
And now he gets his own phone out of his pocket.
就是迈克  我看到他了
It was Mike. I saw him.
你为什么要那么说
Why would you say that?
好吧  行了
Okay, that's it.
上车去  我们不是来干这个的
Get in the car. We didn't come for this.
我是  我们要把事情理清楚
I did. We're sorting things.
这并不能理清什么
This doesn't sort anything!
回车上去
Get in the car.
走吧
Come on.
黛茜
Daisy!
不会发生什么坏事的  好吗
Look, nothing bad's gonna happen, okay?
我保证
I promise, I give you my word.
但我那晚的确那么对黛茜说了
But that is what I said to Daisy that night.
而且
And...
我真不该那么说  因为
it was such a terrible thing to say and do because...
是我拿了埃拉的手机发了那些照片
I took Ella's phone and sent those pictures.
是我
It was me.
我干的
I did it.
都是我干的
All of it.
但为什么
But why?
我看到迈克
I saw Mike...
跟埃拉说话
talking to Ella.
那又如何
Well, even so...
我喜欢迈克
I like Mike.
我喜欢他  我就想"他...
I like him and I thought, "Oh, he's...
要跟埃拉好了"
gone off with Ella."
埃拉才14
Ella-- Ella's 14.
但我希望他注意我
But I wanted him to look at me.
他不了解我的感情
He doesn't know what I feel.
好吧
Okay, listen--
不  我伤害了好多人
No, I've hurt so many people.
现在无法弥补了  怎么能呢
And it can't be put right, how can it?
看这时间  我妈要回来了
The time... My mom will be back.
如果你还没走...
And if you're here...
-你不能在这里  -好
- You can't be. - Okay.
你不能在这里
You can't be here.
-我这就走  -你必须走
- Okay, I'm going. - You have to go.
但我们得谈谈
But we need to talk.
我不是为这个而来
And I didn't come here for this.
我是想来问问你还好吗
I came to see if you were all right.
因为我知道你今早其实在家
'Cause I know you were here this morning
虽然你妈说你在医院
when your mom said you were in hospital.
我这就走  好吗
I'm going, okay?
但我说真的
But I mean that.
我只想帮你
I just wanna help.
我还能告诉你件事
There's something else I can tell you.
听着
Look, um...
你记得吗  我说了
Do you remember, I told you
那个陌生人身边还有个金发女人
that there was a blond woman with the stranger?
她开的车
She was driving the car?
对  她叫英格丽·普利斯比
Right. Well, her name's Ingrid Prisby.
英格丽·普利斯比或盖布莉尔·邓巴
Ingrid Prisby or Gabrielle Dunbar.
吉连追踪她到温莎锁商务园
Killane tracked her to Windsor Lock Business Park.
她是个私家侦探
She's a... private investigator.
我也在那里看到了她  但她开车甩掉了我
And I saw her there, but she... she drove off and I lost her.
我只知道这些了
That's all I know.
马丁·吉连帮了你吗
Martin Killane helped you?
在此之前  只有他在帮我
He's the only one that's been helping me until now.
找到那陌生人怎么就能找到你妻子了
So how will getting to the stranger help find your wife?
一切因她而起
All of this started with her.
我觉得她还知道更多事
I think she knows more.
她肯定知道
She has to.
我会查的
I'll look into it.
谢谢
Thanks.
-喂  -韦斯
- Hello? - Wes.
喂  乔
Hello, Jo.
我能拿走吗
Can I take it?
柯琳·普莱斯的钥匙链
The Corinne Price key fob...
在海蒂·道伊尔凶案现场发现的那个
found at the Heidi Doyle crime scene...
是谁发现的
who found it?
为什么没登记
And why isn't it logged?
各位
Hello?!
亚当·普莱斯的妻子没拿走护照
Adam Price's wife didn't take her passport.
怎么了
What's happened?
柯琳的车被找到了
They found Corinne's car.
后座上还有一只她的耳环
And one of her earrings was in the back seat.
谢谢你照顾瑞恩
Thanks for having Ryan.
家里一窝人呢  托马斯也在
It's a full house. Thomas is here too.
进来吧
Come inside. Come inside.
谢谢
Thanks.
迈克应该会很...
I think that Mike is gonna be pretty...
瑞恩真棒
Ryan's been brilliant.
我们正要开饭  怎么样
We're about to eat. How's that?
嗯  那太好了
Yeah, sounds great, actually.
我想知道的是
What I was wondering is...
你们是否见过这个
if either of you have seen this before.
就是在地板上这里发现的
It was found on the floor in this area.
没有  我扫过这里的地  有我会看到的
No. I swept up in here. I'd have seen that.
抱歉
Sorry.
没事
No, no worries.
那么她被杀前
What about the days...
那几天里呢
leading up to her murder?
你们是否注意到任何异常
Did you notice anything unusual?
最后那晚海蒂看上去如何
How was Heidi that last night?
精神很好
In great spirits.
她当时好像在跟她丈夫打电话
I think she was on the phone to her husband and,
她笑得很开心
you know, she was laughing. And...
你知道的
you know...
之前那晚呢
And the night before?
我们在给你做蛋糕
We were making your cake.
蛋糕  是啊
Cake, of course.
她看上去不像在担心什么吗
She didn't seem concerned about anything?
也没提有什么钱的问题
No mention of money worries?
她是否提到她第二天要去见女儿
Did she say she was gonna see her daughter the next day?
金柏莉吗  没
Kimberley? No.
她整晚上都有说有笑的
She spent the whole evening laughing and joking.
对  在停车场里跟那俩女人也是
Yeah. Even in the car park with those two women.
对  没错
Yeah, that's right. Yeah.
什么女人  什么停车场  什么时候
What women? What car park? When?
她就停在这里
She was parked here.
那俩女人就在这里
And the two women were here.
我们在那边
We were over there.
还有...
And...
-老板  -韦斯  兰顿街停车场
- Hello, boss. - Wes, Renton Street car park.
兰顿街停车场
So Renton Street car park?
我需要他们监控的录像
I need the footage from their CCTV cameras.
-什么时候的  -海蒂·道伊尔被杀前晚
- When? - The night before Heidi Doyle's murder.
约晚7点到午夜
Between 1900 hours and midnight.
找什么
Looking for what?
两个女人  跟海蒂·道伊尔搭话
Two women meeting Heidi Doyle.
好  我就办
Okay, I'm on it.
那是市议会的停车场吧
It's a council car park, isn't it?
对
Uh, yeah.
你不是刚要下班吗
Weren't you just clocking off?
没事
Oh, you're okay.
我想帮忙
I wanna help.
你好  雪松田市议会
Hello, Cedarfield Council.
好了  瑞恩
All right, Ryan,
直接上床去  都11:30了
straight to bed, it's half eleven.
我还没做作业呢
I haven't done my homework.
没事  我给你写个条
It's all right, I'll write a note.
爸爸  我有一堆作业呢
Dad, I've got loads of homework.
我有一堆字条呢
I've got loads of notes.
给
Here you go.
该死的
Bloody hell.
如果你想  我们可以轮班
Listen, we can do this in shifts, if you like.
一人一小时
Hour on, hour off.
-真的吗  -嗯
- Yeah? - Yeah.
反正我喝足了咖啡因  你去休息吧
I'm all caffeined up anyway so go, get your head down.
我一小时后叫醒你
I'll wake you up in an hour, yeah?
你太棒了
Legend.
行了  伙计  睡觉了  太晚了
Come on, mate, it's bedtime. It's late.
我知道  但我能跟你谈谈吗
Yeah. I know. But can I talk you about something?
当然  说吧
Yeah, of course, anything.
好
Okay.
-妈妈是跟人跑了吗  -什么
- Has Mom gone off with someone? - What?
你说什么呢  不是
What are you talking about? No.
但大部分婚姻不都是因此破裂的吗
But isn't that why most marriages break up?
我知道还有其他因素
I mean, I know it's lots of other things as well,
但最终都是这样  是吧
but that's what happens in the end, right?
人们会出轨  然后认真了起来
People have affairs and then it gets serious.
你妈妈没在出轨
Your mom is not having an affair.
人们往往不知道  是吧
People often don't know, do they?
或许是那个教师大会的什么人呢
I mean, maybe it was someone at that teachers' conference.
不是
No.
你妈妈绝不会那么做的
Your mom would never do that, ever.
-永远不会  -爸爸
- As in ever. - Dad.
这种事时有发生
It happens all the time.
你以为黛茜的爸妈为什么分手了
Why do you think Daisy's mom and dad split up?
他跟人跑了
He went off with someone
我觉得现在也是这样
and I just think that's what's happening here.
我觉得妈妈是跟人跑了
I think Mom's gone off with someone else.
你现在在哪
Where are you right now?
质量太差
It's really crap quality.
那试试面部识别
Let's try some facial recognition then.
识别什么
To recognize what?
根本看不清脸
Can't make out their faces. It's...
像素太低
It's too grainy.
我们什么都查了
We went through everything.
我们可以分析肢体语言
We can read the body language though.
是怎么了
What is it?
她们告诉你什么了
What did they just tell you?
好  我们得找到这俩女人
Right, we need to find these two women.
其中一个可能是英格丽·普利斯比
One of them could be Ingrid Prisby.
好  我去跟进一下
All right, I'll go follow up
温莎锁商务园
at Windsor Lock Business Park.
好  但然后你要去睡觉
Okay, but then you get some sleep.
我能做什么
What can I do?
去睡个觉
Go and get some sleep.
我没事
I feel fine.
这是你妈被杀前一晚
This is the night before your mom died.
下班后  她走到车边  碰到了这俩女人
After work, she goes to her car and she meets these two women.
你认得她们吗
Do you recognize them?
然后发生了这个
Then this happens.
她们递给了她什么  她的腿都软了
They hand her something and it's like her knees go.
似乎是在对她们给她看的东西做出反应
Like a reaction to something she's been shown.
是为了避免吵到我爸  他一直在失眠
Um, that's for my dad, 'cause he hasn't been sleeping.
天啊
Oh, my God.
妈妈那天去见我  是因为
Mom came to see me that day because...
有些人
some people...
那些人吧
Uh, those people, I guess...
她们拦下了她  给她看了证据  我在...
they stopped her and gave her proof that I was...
我在为一家
I've been working for this...
甜心网站工作
Sugar Baby site.
是个网站
It's an online thing...
给商人用的
for businessmen.
有时只是跟他们去吃饭  但...
Um, sometimes it's just going out for dinner with them, but...
一般来说
usually...
都是做爱
yeah, it's for sex.
这些找上妈妈的人
And these... these people that spoke to Mom,
她们什么都知道
they knew everything.
她们知道我在固定地见三个人
They knew I was seeing three men on a regular basis,
她们还有我们的短信
they had all our texts,
她们知道我们都在哪  什么时候见面
they knew when and where we met, and...
她们勒索了海蒂
And they were blackmailing Heidi?
要一万英镑
For £10,000.
但她...应该付钱了
But I think... I think she paid it.
所以那晚之后发生的事  应该跟这个无关吧
So whatever happened later that night, that's separate, isn't it?
你见的这三个男人
These three men you were seeing...
我见过妈妈之后
Uh, I contacted them
马上联系了他们  说我不干了
as soon as I'd seen Mom to say I was stopping.
我需要他们的联系方式
I'm gonna need their details.
我们都是在应用上联系的
We only messaged via the app.
我并不知道他们的名字和号码
I don't have names or phone numbers.
我们只有网名
We just have tags.
塔兹  甘达  马贝克40  我是凯蒂
Taz, Gander, Malbec40. I'm Kitty.
你联系他们时
And when you contacted them?
两个人回复了  很担忧
Two replied, really concerned,
说我如果需要帮助会帮我
offering help if I needed it.
第三个呢
And the third one?
他没回复
He didn't reply.
我跟他发了两次消息  因为我们那晚本该见面
I messaged him twice because we were meeting that night and...
我去了  以为他没收到消息  但
I went, thinking he hasn't got the message, but...
他没去
he didn't show.
好  我需要你跟我去警局
All right, listen, I'm gonna need you to come in with me.
-抱歉  伊恩  我们吵醒你了吗  -没有
- Sorry, Ian, did we wake you? - No, no, no.
有什么消息吗
Is there news?
还没有  但我们在夜以继日了
No, nothing yet. We are working day and night though.
我知道
I know.
-查到了什么  -亚当·普莱斯提供的
- What have you got? - So this lead from Adam Price
温莎锁商务园的线索
at Windsor Lock Business Park...
那个私家侦探社
The detective agency...
-英格丽  -英格丽·普利斯比
- Ingrid... - Ingrid Prisby.
假名为盖布莉尔·邓巴
Alias, Gabrielle Dunbar.
她的办公室已经清空了
So her office has been cleared out.
我在查侦探社
I've checked into the agency,
但是用离岸账户设立的
but it was set up with an offshore account
所使用的身份并没有任何相关银行账户
so the ID used isn't attached to any sort of bank account
或社会保险号码
or National Insurance number.
就好像根本没存在过咯
So it's as if it never existed.
是啊
Exactly.
-好  谢谢  -回见
- Right. Thanks. - See you later.
你见的那三个男人
You know the three men you were seeing?
你愿意再联系他们一次吗
How would you feel about contacting them again?
其中一个
One of them...
或许能带我们找到勒索你妈妈的那两个女人
might be able to lead us to the two women who met your mom.
你觉得勒索者跟我妈的死有关吗
You think the blackmail's linked to Mom's death?
差不多绝对有
Almost certainly.
联系他们说什么
Contact them and say what?
就要求见面
Ask to meet.
先是那个没回复的
Starting with the one who didn't reply.
-马贝克40  -对
- Malbec40. - Yeah.
你觉得他会来吗
Do you think he'll show up?
有件事...
There was this...
他...
thing he...
总缠着我跟他做
he always pesters me to do with him.
我一直没答应
Which I don't give in to.
我可以说要跟他做那个
I could offer him that.
会一直有人保护你的
You'll be protected at all times.
好  我们做吧
Yes, do it.
好
Yeah.
-祝你今天顺利  亲爱的  -嗯
- Have a good day, darling. - Yes.
回见
See you later.
我是帕特里克·凯兹  我会尽快回电
This is Patrick Katz, I'll call you straight back.
答应他
Accept.
迈克
Mike?
Mike...
迈克  你能听到吗
Mike, can you hear me?
停下了吗
Has it stopped?
我想是的
I think so.
没那么频繁了
It's happening less.
但时不时的
But every so often...
我又回到了嗑迷幻药时的那种状态
...I'm back in PCP land.
回忆起了那晚的事
Remembering things from that night,
我忘记的事
things I'd forgotten.
比如杀那只羊驼
Like killing the alpaca.
我都嗨傻了
I was off my face.
起初  我和羊驼
To begin with, me and the alpaca,
我们是朋友
we were friends.
好朋友
Big pals, amigos,
我们去冒险来着
we're going on an adventure.
但然后...
But then...
我突然觉得  它要吃了我
I suddenly think it's going to eat me.
真的要吃我
I mean, really eat me.
它对我咄咄逼人
It's looming over me...
露出牙齿
with these teeth.
然后就结束了
And it's the end.
我拼命地挥动着
And I just swing the shovel
铲子
as hard as I can.
你不记得其他的了
You don't remember anything else?
不记得了
No.
但最让我害怕的是
But what's freaking me out...
但丁那晚也受伤了
is Dante was hurt that night as well.
他现在陷入了昏迷
He's in a coma...
我完全不记得跟他相关的任何事
and I have zero recall for anything to do with him.
我对但丁最后的记忆是
The last Dante memory I have is...
你和他
you and him...
去林子里了
going off into the woods.
之后发生了什么
What happened after that?
你们去了哪
Where did you go?
你最后见到他是什么时候
When was the last time you saw him?
黛茜
Daisy?
太好了
Oh, great.
我知道你们还在气奥莉薇娅
Look, I know you're still angry with Olivia,
但她要我稍后去见她
but she's asked to see me later.
我想跟她谈谈
And I thought I should talk to her,
-我们先按兵不动  -好
- before anyone says anything. - Yeah, sure.
去吧
Do it.
她是同意了我的话吗
Did she just agree to that?
嗯
Yeah.
我觉得是的
I think she did.
醒醒了
Wakey! Wakey!
来吧  找我们呢
Come on, we're wanted.
-干什么  -叫我们回去上班
- What for? - We've been called back in.
天啊
Oh, God.
-我手机没电了  -嗯
- My phone's out of charge. - Yeah.
该死
Fuck!
给你我的充电器
Have my charger.
-谢谢  -快点的吧
- Thanks. - Get a move on.
该死的
Fucking hell.
大家能不能安静下来
Okay, can everyone settle down, please?
我们的睡美人们  能不能快点
And our sleeping beauties, can you speed it up?
好  找个甜心.com
Okay, FindYourSugarBaby.Com
是一个性爱网站
is a sex site
帮商人和年轻女子牵线
matching businessman with young women.
基本上就是卖淫
It's essentially prostitution.
为了海蒂·道伊尔案
And in connection with the Heidi Doyle murder,
我们要追查一名未知男子
we are after an unknown man
他已安排好在波利塔酒店
who has arranged to meet this woman
见这名女子
at the Bolitar Hotel.
行动很简单
Straightforward op.
主要目标  保护我们的线人
Main priority: protect our source.
跟海蒂·道伊尔有什么联系
Connected to Heidi Doyle how?
海蒂·道伊尔被勒索了
Heidi Doyle was blackmailed
一万英镑
to the tune of £10,000
跟这个找个甜心网站有关
in connection with this FindYourSugarBaby site.
这是海蒂的女儿
And this is Heidi's daughter.
波利塔酒店很受商人的欢迎
Now, the Bolitar Hotel is very popular with businessmen.
我们的目标  40出头
So our target, early 40s,
身材中等  利索的黑发
medium build, smart dark hair,
这样的人肯定很多
is hardly gonna stick out.
他走到线人身边之前估计不会被认出来
He probably won't be identified until he reaches our source.
但要知道这点
Know this about him though:
他用马贝克40这个网名
he uses the tag Malbec40,
网络组追踪这个网名
a tag that the cyber team have been tracking
两年了  因为涉及投资欺诈
for two years over investment scams.
好  各位在酒店的初始位置
Right, your start positions in the hotel...
这太扯了
This is bullshit.
1号桌是本和尼尔
So table one, I've got Ben and Neil.
就像她一个人跟亚当·普莱斯
It's like her going off with Adam Price,
我们头号嫌犯的丈夫  开车来去
husband of our main suspect, on her own.
简直难以置信
It's un-fucking-believable.
凯兹和韦斯  你们是3号桌
Katz and Wes, you're at table three.
所以说你不能调查朋友的凶杀案
This is why you don't investigate the murder of friends.
5号桌  蒂姆和萨尔
Table five, Tim and Sal,
6号桌  夏洛特和泰德
Table six, Charlotte and Ted.
好  大家都清楚任务了吧
Right, we all know what we're doing?
很好  非常感谢  各位
Great. Thanks very much, everybody.
我是拉里·鲍尔斯  请留言  我稍后回电
Hi, this is Larry Powers. Leave a message and I'll call you back.
别玩手机了  好吗
Get off your phone, will you?
我是在融入环境
I'm fitting in.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
再给我们拿杯酒  好吗
Get us another drink, will you?
-这次拿杯好的  -我们在执勤
- Proper one this time. - We're on duty.
对  在酒吧执勤
Yeah, in a bar.
目标还有多久来
When is the target due?
五分钟
Five minutes.
我去要
I'll get one.
两杯双份伏特加
Two double vodkas.
-加冰和柠檬吗  -不
- Ice and lemon? - No.
该死
Fuck.
刀  有刀
Knife! Knife!
别拘捕
Do not resist!
闭嘴
Shut up!
放开我
Get off me!
干什么
What is this?!
放开我
Get off me!
你在干什么
What are you doing?
放开我  放开
Get off of me! Get off!
-不  -不吗
- No. - No?
不是他
No, isn't him.
我以为我看到了刀
I thought I saw a knife.
什么都没有
There's nothing!
-我以为他有刀  -滚出我的视线
- I thought he had a knife. - Just get out of my sight!
不  算了  你被撤掉了
No, no, actually no. Stand down.
你回家去  明天也别来了
I'm sending you home, don't come in tomorrow.
乔
Jo--
别喊我乔
Don't call me Jo!
你真得退一步了
You need to step back from this, seriously.
他只是尽了职
He's just done what any of us would've done.
你对这事太动感情了
This is too personal for you.
你再也不要不接我的电话了
Don't you ever, ever have your phone turned off to me.
你以为你在跟谁说话呢
Who do you think you're talking to?
-你什么意思  -闭嘴
- What do you mean-- - Shut up.
闭嘴  听好
Shut up and listen.
我想通过银行追踪的勒索犯
The blackmailers I was trying to track through the bank....
我的人没能追踪到他们
My contact couldn't trace them.
我们现在怎么办
So what do we do now?
我另想办法
I'll find another way.
我们收工吧
Let's wrap this up.
但丁·甘纳森刚醒了
Dante Gunnarsson's just come round.
-我去吧  -我没事
- Let me go. I can-- - I'm fine.
好吧
All right!
好  好
All right! All right!
不动吉连家  我理解
Leaving Killane's house, I understand.
周边房子  也行  但整个工地
The surrounding houses, okay, but the whole fucking site?!
停止一切拆除
Stopping any demolition?!
这让我损失重大  他们根本不知道
This is costing me a fortune. They have no idea.
我又不是什么外人
It's not like I'm some kind of an outsider or something.
这是我的街道
This was my street.
吉连夫妇曾是我的朋友  曾经也是好朋友
The Killanes were friends. They were good friends once.
所以  表示尊重
So, due respect,
我是最能理解的
I understand better than anyone here,
但也不能停止整个施工
but you don't close down the whole operation!
我需要跟你谈谈
I need to talk to you.
就是报复  太武断了
Vindictive! It was arbitrary!
那个负责的女警
That police woman in charge...
态度傲慢  我见过太多次了
There's an attitude. I've seen it so many times before!
真的
I kid you not,
他们就是不放过任何让你难受的机会
they will take any opportunity to kick you where it hurts.
-柯琳失踪了  -什么
- Corinne's missing. - What?
柯琳失踪了
I said Corinne's missing.
她不见了
She's gone. She...
她已经消失六天了  我不知道她在哪
She's been gone for about six days. I don't know where she is.
-你怎么没说  -我这不说了
- Why didn't you say? - I'm saying it now.
-好吧  -我需要问你件事
- Okay. - Look, I need to ask you something.
我并不知道推动此事的公司是你的
I didn't know you owned the company behind all of this,
-但你说吉连知道  -是的  我都说了
- but you think Killane did, right? - Yeah, I said so.
你觉得那是他雇我的原因吗
Do you think that's why he hired me,
因为他以为那能阻止你
because he thought it might stop you?
是的  可能的
Yeah, it's feasible.
但那跟柯琳有什么关系
But what would that have to do with Corinne?
或许他还绑架了她
Maybe he got to her too.
他...
He was...
之前在帮我找她
helping me look for her.
一直跟我扯什么
Kept spouting all this bullshit
有些女人走了就不回来了
about sometimes women leave and they don't come back,
结果一直以来  他自己的老婆...
and all the time his own wife was...
他还骗了我什么
What else has he been lying to me about?
我觉得他知道什么关于柯琳的事
I think he knows something about Corinne
没有告诉我
that he's not telling me.
我们得找他谈
We have to talk to him.
我知道
I know.
警探
Detective.
怎么  发生什么了
Why? What's happened?
哪家医院
Which hospital?
怎么...
What...?
怎么了
What's happened?
马丁·吉连刚刚自杀未遂
Martin Killane just tried to commit suicide.
我得走了
I've gotta go.
先生  你不能进来
Sir, you're not allowed here.
我得找他问问我妻子的事  他之前在帮我
I just need to talk to him about my wife. He was helping me.
他被打了麻药
He's sedated.
妈妈上晚课
Mom does evening classes.
数学和生物
Maths and biology.
她想做个护士
She wants to be a nurse.
我等到她走了才来的
I waited till she went.
你就像你妈妈
You're like your mom.
是吧
Aren't you?
她就担心我经常生病的事
She's been worried about me being ill so often,
你也很好心
and you're kind...
就像她
like her.
她还问我要不要
She even asked if I wanted to see
再去找别的医生看看
another doctor for a second opinion.
我妈妈不想那么做
I mean, my mom didn't like that.
我们就没去  但
So we didn't, but...
她真是好心
it was nice of her.
你为什么经常生病
Why are you ill so often?
他们不知道
They don't know.
但你都在服什么药
But what medication are you on?
我妈妈负责那个
My mom does that.
并不多
It's not much.
抗生素和治恶心的药
Antibiotics and stuff for nausea.
那么是谁在服那么多药  你妈妈吗
Right, so who takes all the medicine around here? Your mom?
我妈妈
My mom?
没有啊
No.
我是想谈埃拉和迈克的事
No, look, I wanted to talk about Ella and Mike.
会说到那个的  但是
We will, but listen...
听你妈妈撒谎说你在医院后
After your mom said you were in hospital and you weren't,
我们看到她丢掉了大量的处方药盒
we saw her throwing out these boxes of prescription drugs,
还有好多盒老鼠药
and even boxes of rat poison.
而且不是扔在你们自家垃圾箱里
And not in your own bin.
什么意思
What do you mean?
肯定是我妈妈
I bet that's my mom.
她会回来查我岗  去藏起来
She does this to check on me. Go hide in there, go.
爸爸  你怎么来了
Dad, what are you doing here?
亲爱的  你好吗
Hi, darling. How are you?
我不会久留
Listen, I'm not stopping, okay?
-你去哪  -我得开我的车
- Uh, where are you going? - I need to get my car.
-爸爸  -亲爱的  听我说
- Dad, um-- - Sweetheart, listen to me.
我很快就要有钱了  好吗
Very soon I'm gonna come into some money, okay?
我会更经常地陪伴你  我保证
And I'm gonna be around a lot more for you, I promise.
你和我会一起做好多很棒的事
And you and me are gonna do such great things together.
我保证
I promise you.
我想过去...
I'm trying to get through--
不行  抱歉  这一区暂不接待探病者
No, sorry, this area is currently closed to visitors.
你得回前台的保安处
You'll need to go back down to security at the front desk
获得批准
and get authorization.
抱歉  亲爱的
Sorry, love.
我得请您马上走  先生
I'm telling you to leave now, sir.